pxg.com 2019-05-03

# Privacy Policy - PXG

Parsons Xtreme Golf - Privacy Notice

Last Updated: May 23, 2018

Parsons Xtreme Golf, LLC, PXG UK Limited, and PXG Canada Limited ("PXG", "we", "us", or "our") is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust as it relates to the privacy of your information. Please read below and learn how we collect, use and share your information on this website and its web pages (collectively, the "Site"), and how we collect, use and share your information in the course of fitting you for PXG products and ultimately building and providing those products to you (the "Services").

### 1\. The Information We Collect

**Information You Provide To Us:** We, or our service providers (acting on our behalf), may collect "Personal Information" (which is information that, on its own or when combined with other information, can be used to identify you) that you provide to us.

For example, the Personal Information we collect in the course of providing the Services to you depends on how you engage with our Services:

Ordering through PXG.com (" **Website Order** ")

  * contact details (first and last name; email address; telephone number(s); and postal address);
  * measurements taken by you (if ordering direct through our e-commerce site); and
  * any Personal Information you include in correspondence with us about the Services.

Ordering through PXG Fitters (" **Fitter Order** ")

  * contact details (first and last name; email address; telephone number(s); and postal address);
  * correspondence directly with PXG Fitter(s);
  * club fitting measurements taken by PXG Fitter(s) to provide you with the Services; and
  * any Personal Information you include in correspondence with us about the Services.

Ordering on-site at a Golf Club (" **Club Order** ")

  * contact details (first and last name; email address; telephone number(s); and postal address);
  * club fitting measurements taken by a Golf Club employee or contractor;
  * membership details of the Golf Club; and
  * any Personal Information you include in correspondence with us about the Services.

**Information Collected Automatically:** Whenever you visit or interact with the Site, we, as well as our third-party service providers, may use a variety of technologies that automatically or passively collect information about how you access and use the Site. This may include:

  * Your IP address or other unique identifier for the computer, mobile phone, tablet or other device you use to access the Site.
  * Device type.
  * Your location.
  * The type of browser software and operating system you are using.
  * The web page(s) you have accessed, and the time you accessed them.

Collecting this information enables us to better understand the visitors who come to our Site, where they come from, and what content on our Site is of interest to them. We use this information for our internal analytics purposes and to improve the quality and relevance of our Site to our visitors.

**Cookies:** For more information about the use of Cookies and Other Technology on our online services (including your opt-out choices) please see the Cookies and Tracking Technologies Notice.

**Information from Third Parties:** From time to time, we may receive Personal Information about you from third party sources, but only where we have checked that these third parties either have your consent or are otherwise legally permitted or required to disclose your Personal Information to us.

For example, we partner with i-Parcel, a service provided by UPS. i-Parcel is the third-party service provider we use to deliver certain products to you, and as such we may collect information from them about your order so that we can ensure our products are delivered effectively, accurately and safely. UPS is a US headquartered company (please see section 7 of this notice, below, for more information on international transfers).

### 2\. How We Use Your Personal Information

We use the Personal Information we collect about and from you:

  * To build and deliver your PXG products and provide you with the Services.
  * To enable us to run the Site. For example, we may use your Personal information: to complete and fulfil any purchases or requests for products or Services; to respond to your questions and requests; to communicate with you about changes to any PXG policy or notice; and to improve the Site and keep it secure.
  * To personalize your PXG experience, including: to tailor content, advertisements, and offers we serve you; and for market research and statistical analysis.
  * To comply with our legal obligations, to enforce our terms and conditions, and to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others.
  * To help us to administer the Site and fix problems.
  * To analyze trends, and to track your web page movements in order to keep the Site fresh and interesting for you.

### 3\. Sharing Information

We may share your Personal Information with the third parties set out below in the following circumstances:

  * **Group companies and third-party service providers:** We instruct our group companies, other companies and individuals to perform activities on our behalf. Examples may include sharing details with professionals who may assist in taking your measurements so that we can deliver the Services, sending email, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance and providing customer service.
  * **Business Transfers:** We may share your Personal Information if we wish to sell, or reorganise our business, or if we become insolvent (including with third parties that may wish to buy our company).
  * **Competent law enforcement bodies, regulatory, government agencies, court or other third party:** We may transfer and disclose your Personal Information to third parties to comply with a legal obligation, to make sure you are complying with our Terms of Use or other applicable policies to investigate possible fraud, or to help investigate or fix any security or technical issues relating to the Site, or to respond to an emergency; or otherwise to protect our rights or property or the security of third parties, visitors to our Site, or the public.

We may also share your data with anyone else, as long as we have consent to such an arrangement.

### 4\. Our Legal Basis for Processing Your Personal Information (European Economic Area (“EEA”) Customers Only)

We will only ever use your Personal Information:

  * to perform a contract we have with you (for example, if you purchase goods from the Site, we will need to use your Personal Information to process your order and to enable delivery).
  * if it is in our legitimate interests to do so (for example, to let you know about certain products or services you may be interested in, to carry out market research, or to share your Personal Information with our third-party service providers to help us provide our services, sell our products and operate the Site), but where those interests do not override your rights.
  * if you have given us your consent (in which case we will tell you at the time how we intend to use your Personal Information). If you have given us your consent to use your Personal Information in a particular way, you may withdraw it any time by contacting us using the contact details below.
  * to comply with a legal obligation.

If we ask you to provide Personal Information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contact with you, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your Personal Information is mandatory or not (as well as of the possible consequences if you do not provide your Personal Information).

### 5\. Third-Party Links

The Site may contain links to other sites that we are not responsible for such as Facebook, Instagram, and Twitter. We do not control, recommend or endorse these other sites. These other sites may also collect Personal Information about you, and they may have their own privacy policies. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of any site that you access through our Site.

### 6\. Children

This Site is a general audience website and is not designed for or directed at children. As such, we do not knowingly process Personal Information about children under 13 years of age.

### 7\. We may transfer your Personal Information to the United States

If you are located in the European Union, Canada or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that we are a United States based company. Our Site servers are located in the United States and our group companies and third-party service providers and partners (such as UPS) operate around the world, so when we collect your Personal Information we may process it in any of the countries where our group companies and third parties are based.

However, we have taken appropriate safeguards to require that your Personal Information will remain protected in accordance with this Privacy Notice. These measures include transferring your personal data to third parties who are located in a country which the European Commission has determined has data protection laws that are at least as protective as those in Europe, and transferring your personal data to third parties who have entered into standard contractual clauses with us. For more information about these safeguards please contact us using the contact details provided below.

Your information will be protected under the European Commission’s Standard Contractual Clauses for transfers of Personal Information between our group companies, which require all of our group companies to protect Personal Information they process from the EEA in accordance with European Union data protection law.

### 8\. How long do we keep your Personal Information?

Where we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your Personal Information, we will either delete or anonymise it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your Personal Information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your Personal Information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible. You can request deletion of your Personal Information at any time by contacting us using the contact details set out below.

### 9\. How do we keep your Personal Information secure?

We use appropriate technical and organisational measures to protect the Personal Information that we collect and process about you. The measures we use are designed to provide a level of security appropriate to the risk of processing your Personal Information. Specific measures we use include encrypting your Personal Information in transit and at rest.

### 10\. Your Rights and Choices

**Access.** You have the right to access the Personal Information we hold about you. If you wish to obtain a copy or description of the Personal Information we hold about you, please let us know in writing (e.g., email or by post) using the contact details set out below. We may also ask you to verify your identify and to provide further details about your request.

**Accuracy.** We will do our best to ensure the Personal Information we retain about you is accurate. It is your responsibility to ensure that you submit true, accurate and complete information to us. We may from time to time send you an email update to remind you to tell us about any updates or changes to your Personal Information. You have the right to request that any inaccurate Personal Information is corrected and any incomplete information is completed by contacting us using the contact details set out below. You have the right to correct or update your Personal Information.

**Deletion Requests.** You have the right to request that we delete Personal Information that we hold about you. If you would like us to erase the Personal Information that we hold about you, please contact us using the contact details set out below.

**Other Rights.** You can object to processing of your Personal Information, ask us to restrict processing of your personal information or request portability of your Personal Information. Again, you can exercise these rights by contacting us using the contact details provided below.

**Consent.** Similarly, if we have collected and process your Personal Information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your Personal Information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.

### 11\. Withdrawing Your Consent to Receive Marketing Messages

You may ask us to stop using your Personal Information for advertising or marketing purposes at any time. If you wish to do this, please send us an email to privacy@pxg.com with "UNSUBSCRIBE" in the subject line or click the “unsubscribe from this list” link in any of our emails.

### 12\. Changes

We may update this Privacy Notice to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will provide you with a prominent notification prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

You can see when this Privacy Notice was last updated by checking the “last updated” date displayed at the top of this Privacy Notice.

### 13\. Queries or Complaints

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Notice, this Site, or about our use of your Personal Information, please contact us using the contact details set out below. In addition (if you are from the EEA), if you have any complaints about how we use your Personal Information, you may also contact the Information Commissioner's Office (the "ICO"). Contact details for the ICO may be found on the ICO's website, which may be accessed via the following link: https://ico.org.uk/

### 14\. Our Contact Details

If you wish to contact us you may do so using the following contact details:

By email: privacy@pxg.com.

Address:   
15485 N 83rd Way  
Scottsdale, Arizona 85260

If you place a Website Order, Club Order (outside of the EEA) or a Fitter Order (outside of the EEA), the data controller of your Personal Information is Parsons Xtreme Golf, LLC.

If you place a Fitter Order (within the EEA) or a Club Order (within the EEA), the data controller of your Personal Information is PXG UK Limited.

If you place a Fitter Order (within Canada) or a Club Order (within Canada), the data controller of your Personal Information is PXG Canada Limited.
